qlinkwireless.com 2019-05-06

# None

Q Link Wireless is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the ways in which Q Link Wireless uses and protects the information we collect about our Customers and our Users.

## Information We Collect and How We Use It

Q Link Wireless collects and uses information about our subscribers and website visitors based on your use of our products and services and our business relationship with you, and when you make online inquiries into our service.

Q Link Wireless uses such information to provide you with the ability to sign up for products and services; to provide you with the highest quality customer experience possible; and to communicate with our subscribers regarding service updates, offers, and promotions. We also use this information for third party advertising; prevention of fraud or illegal activities to prevent or investigate violations of our Terms and Conditions; to respond to your questions; to develop network integrity and for security procedures. Q Link Wireless will, disclose customer identifiable information as required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process or in the event that such customer is engaging in unlawful use of our website. When Q Link Wireless uses third parties to perform services on its behalf, Q Link Wireless cannot ensure that all of your customer identifiable information will never be disclosed, as regulatory and/or other requirements may make disclosure necessary.

## How We Collect Information

Q Link Wireless collects information about all activity on its websites using cookies, server log files, web beacons, website widgets and other technologies. Anytime anyone visits our website, we may obtain and capture information that may allow us to identify you via cookies, server log files, web beacons, website widgets and other technologies. If you do not wish to utilize cookies, you have the ability to disable this feature within your individual web browser. However, by disabling cookies, a customer will not have access to certain areas of our website through the cookie-disabled browser.

## Contact Information

By applying for service, you agree to be contacted by Q Link Wireless, our affiliates, and/or any government agencies, even if you appear on a Do Not Call List. You may be contacted by phone, automated dialers, IVR system, email, text, push notifications, direct mail, or any other form of communication.

Contact Information can consist of:

  * Information that allows us to communicate with you and can include your name, address, telephone number, and email address.
  * Billing information can include your payment data, credit history, credit card number, Social Security numbers, security codes, and service history.

## TCPA DISCLOSURE

To ensure that consumer’s inquiries are handled promptly, courteously, and accurately, some of the phone calls between you and us or any of our affiliates, agents, assigns and service providers, may be monitored and recorded by us and any of our affiliates, agents, assigns and service providers, to enhance service to you. You consent to this monitoring and recording. You agree that Q Link may from time to time make calls and/or send text messages to you at any telephone numbers associated with your account, including wireless telephone numbers that could result in charges to you. The manner in which these calls or text messages are made to you may include, but is not limited to, the use of prerecorded/artificial voice messages and/or automatic telephone dialing system. You further agree that Q Link may send e-mails to you at any e-mail address you provide us or use other electronic means of communication to the extent permitted by law. Consent may be revoked at any time and by any reasonable means.

## Third Party Websites

websites may from time to time contain links to other websites. As such, we cannot be responsible for the content or privacy practices of third party websites. Third party websites may collect personal information from our customers and as such, you should be aware of the privacy policies of all third party websites.

## Information Not Covered

Information that you provide to non-Q Link Wireless companies is not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you download applications or make an online purchase from a non-Q Link Wireless company while using Q Link Wireless' Internet or wireless services, the information collected by the non-Q Link Wireless company is not subject to this Privacy Policy; use of public forums such as social networking services, Internet bulletin boards, chat rooms, or blogs. Any personal information you disclose publicly can be read, collected, or used by others. If you choose to reveal personal information, Q Link Wireless cannot prevent distribution and use of that information by other parties. Additionally, if you are a Q Link Wireless subscriber who is roaming on the network of a non-Q Link Wireless company, information about your location, usage, and the numbers you dial will not be subject to the Q Link Wireless Privacy Policy.

## Our Online Privacy Policy for Children

Q Link Wireless does do not knowingly collect personally identifying information from anyone under the age of thirteen (13) unless that child's parent or legal guardian is utilizing the child's information knowingly as a means to attempt to gain services. In this situation, any information collected will appear to be the personal information of the actual adult subscriber and treated as such under this Privacy Policy. Q Link Wireless does not collect any information from anyone under the age of thirteen (13) that is not submitted to us. Q Link Wireless' cellular devices and services may be used by minors without the knowledge of Q Link Wireless.

## Safeguarding Your Personal Information

Q Link Wireless does not sell any personally identifiable information to third parties. Q Link Wireless only maintains information about you in our business records while you are a customer, or until it is no longer needed for business, tax, or legal purposes. However, some federal and state rules require us to maintain personally identifiable information on our subscribers for up to five (5) years after you have ceased your business relationship with us.

## California Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of California, certain rules apply to your privacy rights. California state regulations entitle California subscribers to request information concerning whether a business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. California customers who wish to request further information about our compliance with this law or have questions or concerns about our privacy practices and policies may contact us in writing via mail or via fax to:

**BY MAIL:** Q Link Wireless LLC  
499 E SHERIDAN ST, STE 200  
DANIA, FLORIDA 33004  
USA  

**BY FAX:**  
1-855-837-5465  

## Privacy Policy Changes

Q Link Wireless reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy from time to time by publishing new terms on its website at any time and your access and use of the Q Link Wireless website thereafter constitutes your acknowledgment and acceptance of such amended policy. This Privacy Policy does not create any legal right for you or any third parties.

## Customer Proprietary Network Information (CPNI)

Customer Proprietary Network Information (CPNI) is information that Q Link Wireless obtains when providing your telecommunications services to you. CPNI is information that relates to the quantity, configuration, type, destination, location, and amount of use of the telecommunications services provided by Q Link Wireless as well as the information contained in subscriber bills for those services. CPNI includes the types of telecommunications services you currently purchase, how you use them, and the billing information related to those services, including items such as the types of local, long distance and wireless telecommunications services that you have purchased and your calling details. **Your telephone number, name, and address are not considered CPNI.**

Q Link Wireless obtains and collects CPNI in the normal course of providing you with telecommunications services. We may, from time to time, use your CPNI to offer you additional services of the type you already purchase from Q Link Wireless. We also may use your CPNI to offer you products and services, packages, discounts, and promotions that may be different from the types of services you have already purchased.

Q Link Wireless may use this information for certain purposes as allowed by law without further disclosure or consent including but not limited to the following: to provide you service; to market service offerings to you related to the services you purchase; to protect you, other Q Link Wireless users, Q Link Wireless, and other carriers from fraud, abuse or unlawful use of its service. In accordance with applicable law, Q Link Wireless reserves the right to communicate with you by using pre-recorded messages that are informational or promotional in nature.

Q Link Wireless may also share information with its affiliates and third party agents for the limited purpose of making available to you communications-related offers and information that may be of interest to you.

Q Link Wireless does not disclose CPNI outside of the Q Link Wireless companies or their agents without customer consent, except as required or allowed by law. However Q Link Wireless does utilize third parties to perform services on its behalf that require the use of CPNI.

## Restricting Our Use of Your CPNI

If you wish to restrict our use of your CPNI for marketing purposes, known as an "opt out" request, you may do so by requesting a restriction of your CPNI in writing via mail or via fax to:

**BY MAIL:** Q Link Wireless LLC  
499 E SHERIDAN ST, STE 200  
DANIA, FLORIDA 33004  
USA  

**BY FAX:**  
1-855-837-5465  

Restricting our use of your CPNI for marketing purposes will not affect the provision of any Q Link Wireless products or services to which you subscribe, nor will it eliminate all types of Q Link Wireless marketing contacts.

## Advertisements

Advertisements may appear on Q Link Wireless website pages from time to time. Some advertisements may request information directly from our customers or take our customers to websites that may request personal information. Q Link Wireless is in no way responsible for these advertisers' privacy policies, so please examine the Privacy Policy of any company advertising on our websites prior to submitting any personal information.

## Account Information

Q Link Wireless will reply to requests from customers for account information and will correct any such information, which may from time to time be inaccurate. Subscribers may contact Q Link Wireless to verify that appropriate corrections have been made.

## Email Communications

Q Link Wireless does not disclose to third parties email communications that are transmitted using Q Link Wireless services, except as required to provide the service or as otherwise authorized or required by law.

Q Link Wireless may, from time to time, send our subscribers emails or text messages regarding promotional offers or other information. A customer has the right to elect not to receive Q Link Wireless email direct marketing communications by simply opting-out or unsubscribing to the email offerings. These requests should be in writing via mail or via fax:

**BY MAIL:**  
Q Link Wireless LLC  
499 E SHERIDAN ST, STE 200  
DANIA, FLORIDA 33004  
USA  

**BY FAX:**  
1-855-837-5465 

## Use of Location Information

When your Q Link Wireless cellular device is on, it sends signals to the nearest cell tower. As a result Q Link Wireless may use or disclose your wireless device location information as necessary to respond to calls to 911 or in other emergency-related situations as provided by law. Q Link Wireless endeavors to safeguard the privacy of subscriber identifiable information from unauthorized access or improper use. However, Q Link Wireless cannot at any time provide a guarantee of 100% security.
